Ms Xu.
I'm sorry
you had to go through such a scare
right after coming home.
[Eclipse in the Lost City]
[Episode 18]
Why don't you take a look first?
She is trustworthy.
It is indeed Lu Ye's handwriting.
It's as ugly as ever.
He really does know you.
Lu Ye wants Xu Qingdao dead.
And so do I.
In that case,
why don't we cooperate?
Whatever you want to do
is none of my business.
Anyway, once it's done,
the Shisha Gang is mine.
Nothing else matters.
Why does he trust you?
After everything I said,
is this what you want to ask?
The new lead is at Renji Hospital.
Whether you go is up to you.
It healed that quickly?
Boss, this is bad!
Tianbai's condition has gotten worse!
Take him to the hospital quickly!
[Renji Hospital]
It's nothing serious.
He might run a fever for a few days.
[Director of Renji Hospital]
He needs plenty of rest,
or it could weaken his constitution.
It's normal for it to flare up
from time to time.
After all, most people couldn't
handle something like that.
Compared to most people,
he's actually handling it very well.
That's very thoughtful of you, Chief Xu.
This kid's got one tough life.
Still, it can't have been easy for him.
I'll go check on him.
Dad.
Let me go instead.
I'd like to take care of him for a while.
Okay, Yin.
I'll leave him in your hands.
Please.
Our current experimental data
still needs some...
It's okay.
It's fine.
Easy. It's me.
I...
You're awake?
Can you let me go now?
Sorry.
Don't mention it.
I'm always happy to help,
right?
You...
Are you...
Are you badly hurt?
Did I do this?
I'm sorry. I...
I'm fine.
I checked myself into the hospital
so I could move around more easily.
But Officer Shen,
you already owe me several meals.
Don't try to get out of it.
Okay.
But...
we really need to figure out
why you lost control.
The maintenance dose.
I suspect something was wrong
with the maintenance dose
Xu Qingdao injected me with.
It wasn't the same type as before.
He probably came to the hospital, too.
Be careful.
Don't worry.
I had Xu Yin keep him away.
We...
You really trust her.
Who?
Xu Yin.
Of course.
I almost forgot the important part.
The new lead has something to do
with this hospital's director.
We have a Qingtian Gang informant here.
He gave me this.
[S-03 has been activated. Attached is
this month's S-02 failed-case report.]
[Sample X has also exhibited an anomaly
similar to last month's case.]
The director is connected to Wolfbane.
Dad.
Yin.
Why are you here?
I just went to get the medicine.
Dad.
Why are you back?
You left this in the car.
It's cold at night.
Put this on.
Thank you.
Since I'm here,
I'll go see Tianbai before I leave.
By the way, Dad,
did you forget this?
There it is.
Yin，
don't just focus on taking care of him.
Get some rest yourself.
Yes, Father.
I'll get going, then.
The old geezer
came back just to check up on me.
He's gone.
Lu Ye?
My leg...
My leg is numb.
Help me.
Since when did you get so weak?
You'll know when you reach my age.
He is your sworn enemy?
What do you want to do?
Can we trust a cop?
If you want to cooperate with me,
you have to trust him.
I know exactly what kind of person he is.
Fair enough.
After all, someone used to say that word
all the time when he was abroad.
Don't tell him.
That depends on how you behave.
Alright, I promise you.
Wipe your face clean first.
What's wrong?
Did I miss a spot?
Miss Xu, we have things to do.
We'll get going.
Suit yourself.
Where are you going?
To find someone.
Why?
What?
You kept testing me
before you finally trusted me.
Xu Yin is Xu Qingdao's daughter,
yet you trust her so much.
Didn't she tell you?
Tell me what?
Your relationship?
Yes.
We went to college together.
Don't worry.
She absolutely hates Xu Qingdao
because he was responsible
for her mother's death.
I see.
You guys are all so cautious.
I have to say,
you two are quite a match.
No wonder Xu Qingdao wanted
to set you two up.
Shut up.